ACTWU's Legal Department Records 5619/017
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ACTWU's Legal Department Records
1942-1995
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Legal Department.
Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union. Legal Department.
5619/017
151 cubic feet
151 linear feet
Correspondence, reports, publications.
This collection consists of correspondence, reports, and files from the Legal Department of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America and the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union. Much of the material relates to the Farah and J. P. Stevens campaigns.
6766608
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff
Date completed:
January 2011
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 2011
Biographical / Historical
The Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, the most significant union representing workers in the men's clothing industry, was founded in New York City in 1914 as a breakaway movement from the United Garment Workers. Radical and immigrant workers in the tailors' and cutters' locals were the core of the seceding group, which advocated industrial unionism and economic strikes in opposition to the UGW's craft organization, which they saw as conservative and timid. Their diverging views had come to the fore during the historic 1910 dispute at the Chicago firm Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. The opposition called the strike against the UGW leadership's advice, and reached a path-breaking agreement with management that established an arbitration system to settle disputes.
Members flocked to the new union. Around 50,000 strong at its founding, by 1920 the ACWA counted about 170,000 members. Initially composed mostly of immigrants of Jewish European descent with Socialist leanings, the ACWA quickly welcomed members of a great number of nationalities and diverse backgrounds. Like in other garment unions, most workers and many members were women, but the leadership was predominantly male, a situation that did not change for many decades. Early on the union adopted a centralized administrative structure combined with industrial unionism, with the joint boards' by-laws having precedence over those of locals.
Espousing a philosophy perhaps brought over by its early immigrant socialist members, the Amalgamated went beyond bread and butter issues and adopted a distinctive form of social unionism that was largely absent in the American labor movement. Starting in the 1920s, it provided educational opportunities and recreational facilities for its members, as well as services such as an insurance plan, banks offering personal loans at low interest rates, low-cost housing cooperatives, medical clinics, and even union-owned restaurants.
Sidney Hillman was the first president of the new union and the most important officer in its history. He applied his experience as bargaining representative in Chicago to the whole industry. Under his leadership the union made significant strides in securing better wages and working conditions for its members, and at the same time it consolidated gains and provided stability to the industry through the widespread adoption of the arbitration system tested at Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. Hillman paid close attention to industry issues, such as production, pricing, and marketing. In order to help management meet the competition of non-union firms, the union conducted studies of efficiency, work methods, and factory costs. Letters to the official publication of the union, Advance, document the controversy that ensued within the union over what was perceived to be collaboration with management.
Hillman also understood the importance of labor's involvement in national affairs and political action. In the 1920s the ACWA sent delegates to the Conference for Progressive Political Action and to the Farmer-labor party conventions. Although many members and officers were Socialists, the union stopped short of officially endorsing the party. Communist attempts at gaining influence within the union were firmly curbed. Hillman's participation in national affairs and politics became prominent during the New Deal, when he became a close advisor to Franklin D. Roosevelt on labor and economic issues. He also served on the board of the National Recovery Administration. Later, during World War II, he helped establish the Labor's Non Partisan League. He was also named associate director of the Office of Production Management, which assisted in mobilizing the nation's resources for the war effort. Hillman's prestige perhaps reflected the healthy condition of his union, which by the end of the conflict was strong and stable.
During the post World War II period the union faced a number of significant challenges. Membership continued to grow (peaking at 395,000 in 1968), but the union's political influence and visibility in national affairs declined. In their never ending pursuit of lower production costs, many firms relocated to the South, forcing the union to engage in large organizing efforts. Simultaneously, signs began to appear of changes that would lead to the almost complete demise of the domestic apparel industry and, ultimately, to the erosion of union membership. Foreign imports of cheap clothing goods steadily grew in the 1950s and 1960s, and mushroomed in the following two decades, plunging employment in the apparel sector into a steady decline. Union efforts to stem the tide included Buy American campaigns and extensive lobbying in Congress, but they were to no avail. In 1976, the ACWA merged with the Textile Workers of America to become the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Despite successful and much publicized nationwide actions such as the Farah boycott and the J.P. Stevens corporate campaign, the woes threatening the union's existence continued unabated. The fate of the domestic industry was sealed in the late 1970s and the 1980s by the flight of firms chasing tax breaks and cheap labor abroad. By 1995, when ACTWU voted to merge with the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, their combined membership was 350,000. The new Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE!) seemed poised to infuse new life in a troubled union.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related collections: 5619: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America All other 5619 collections and 6000/019: UNITE's Department of Occupational Safety and Health Records
Clothing workers--Labor unions--New York (State); Clothing trade--New York (State); Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Legal Department --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Legal Department --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union --Archives; United Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE) --Archives; UNITE HERE (Organization) --Archives
6766608
- Boss Manufacturing Company Kewanee-Chillicothe [folder 1 of 3], 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Boss Manufacturing Company Kewanee-Chillicothe [folder 2 of 3], 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Boss Manufacturing Company Kewanee-Chillicothe [folder 3 of 3], 1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Boss Manufacturing Company Insurance, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Boss Manufacturing Company 8(B) Charge Against Amalgamated, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Boss Mfg. Co. Chillicothe, MO Unfair Labor Practice Charge Against ACWA, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Boss Manufacturing Company ULP- Refusal to Hire, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Boss Manufacturing Company Cisco, Texas, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Boss Manufacturing Company NLRB Charges [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Boss Manufacturing Company NLRB Charges [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Boss Manufacturing Company Decertification Petition Transcript & Evidence, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Boss Manufacturing Company Kewanee-Chillicothe, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Scope and Contents
  Jan-Feb. 1966
- Boss Manufacturing Company Kewanee-Chillicothe, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  April 1965
- Boss Manufacturing Company Unfair Labor Practices Hearing & Briefs, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Boss Manufacturing Company Kewanee-Chillicothe, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  September-December 1965
- Boss Manufacturing Company Kewanee-Chillicothe, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  May-August 1965
- Boss Manufacturing Co. Oneida, Tenn. Refusal to Bargain Charge, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Boss Manufacturing Company Kewanee-Chillicothe, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  January-March 1965
- Boss Manufacturing Company Unfair Labor Practices, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  November 1964-1965
- Boss Manufacturing Co. Oneida, Tenn. General, 1963-1968 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Boss Manufacturing Company Kewanee-Chillicothe, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  March-April 1966
- Boss Manufacturing Company Organizing Propaganda, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Boss Manufacturing Co. (Extra Copies) Request for Review, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  November 18, 1964
- Boss Mfg Co, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Boss Manufacturing Co. Hazel Foster Arbitration, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Boss Manufacturing Company Criminal Charges Against Eddie Gee, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Boss Manufacturing Company Injunction, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Boss Manufacturing Company Transcripts, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Boss Mfg. Co. Palm, PA Warehouse Federal Court, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Boss Mfg. Co. Palm, PA Warehouse (Trucking Injunction) State Court, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Ratner Corporation, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- A. Phillip Randolph Institute, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  1/10/73-12/18/74
- ACWA Organizing Retail, 1969-1975 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- FARAH: Scandinavia, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Organizing: Targets, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- FARAH: Publications, correspondence., 1973 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Boss Manufacturing Co., 1973 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Riverbay Corporation, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- United Housing Foundation, 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- ACWA: Staff Institute, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  10/1973
- Botany: General, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Botany Industries Lawsuit, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Rapid American Corporation, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Botany: Bankruptcy, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- FARAH: Publications, Xerox Copies, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- IUD (1 of 4), 1961 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- IUD (2 of 4), 1961 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- IUD (3 of 4), 1961 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- IUD (4 of 4), 1961 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- IUD, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- AFL-CIO- Exec. Council Minutes Unity House, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- IUD, AFL-CIO Convention, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- AFL-CIO (1 of 5), 1961 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- AFL-CIO (2 of 5), 1961 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- AFL-CIO (3 of 5), 1961 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- AFL-CIO (4 of 5), 1961 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- AFL-CIO (5 of 5), 1961 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Catholic- Background Material (1 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Catholic- Background Material (2 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Catholic-Jesuits, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Fr. Bauer's Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Endorsements & Endorsers - Catholic (1 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Endorsements & Endorsers - Catholic (2 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Inter-Faith, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Edward Kennedy on FARAH, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Literature- Farah- Other ACWA, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Father Lyons - Bibliography, 1970-1974 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Metzger Ads, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Post-Farah Boycott, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Contact Lists R.C., 1973 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Archives, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  March 1974
- May Co., 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Farah Strike Activities, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Farah Agreement, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  Letters, News Clippings, etc.
- Farah Leaflets & Ads, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Staff Assigned by AFL-CIO Unions & Thank You Letters, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- NAT AFL-CIO Boycott, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- AFL-CIO Boycott, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- NAT'L- AFL- CIO, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Union Label & Service Trade Dept. AFL-CIO, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- CLC's & Report Forms, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- CLC's AFL-CIO Directory, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  July 1972
- CA $s by Area, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- New Campaign, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Farah Winter Campaign (1 of 4), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Farah Winter Campaign (2 of 4), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Farah Winter Campaign (3 of 4), 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Farah Winter Campaign (4 of 4), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Retail Cancellations (1 of 3), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Retail Cancellations (2 of 3), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Retail Cancellations (3 of 3), 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Caravan, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Week Caravan, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Celebrities, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Chains- Lists of Directors, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Chain Stores, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Chains As Listed In Fairchild Manual, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Chain Store List, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Mfg. Who Own Retail Stores, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  April 1972
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Retail Chain List, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Chains Retail Lists Misc., 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. ACWA (1 of 2), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. ACWA (2 of 2), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Operation Clean Sweep (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Operation Clean Sweep (2 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Ads, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Contributions, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Coordinators, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Daire (Farah) Line, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. EL Paso Accepts & Thank You, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Refusals, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Invitations to El Paso, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  9/25/1973
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Father's Day Demos, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  June 1973
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Father's Day Ads, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Summary Master List, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Adoption of Farah Employees, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Aquiler v. Farah (Negligence), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Background, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Brief to the Regional Director Case #23-RC-3826, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Briefs 28-CA-1886 & 28-CA-1977, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Case # 23-CA-4389 (1 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Case no.23-CA-4389 (2 of 2), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Farah Clippings, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Farah Clips, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  May 10, 1972 thru March 9, 1973
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Citizens Committee for Farah Workers, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Economic & International, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Equal Employment, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Las Cruces, New Mexico Litigation, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Albuquerque, New Mexico Litigations, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Machine Shop (1 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Machine Shop (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Extra Copies of Brief Machine Shop 28-RC-2312, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Machine Shop 28-RC-2312 (1 of 4), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Machine Shop 28-RC-2312 (2 of 4), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Machine Shop 28-RC-2312 (3 of 4), 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Machine Shop 28-RC-2312 (4 of 4), 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Case #28-RC-2312 Employers Request for Review, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Nash-Finch-Remedy, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. New Charges 8(A) 1-2-3-4-5, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  December 12-13, 1973
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Northwest Work Stoppage 28-CA-2577, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Northwest Work Stoppage 28-CA-2577 (Working Materials), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Farah Pension Plan, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Civil Rights Action 42 USC 1981, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. El Paso Joint Board Petition for Certiorari, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. "Persuaders", 1973 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Publicity "Boycott" (1 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Publicity "Boycott" (2 of 2), 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Farah-ACWA-Publicity, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Newspaper Clippings, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. San Antonio - Garza 28-CA-2754, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. ULP- Santa E, Rodriques, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Case no.28-CC-449 "Scoggins" 28-CC-451 "Farah", 1973 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Shopping Center Picketing, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  September 14, 1973
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Strike Relief Voluntary Checkoff Forms, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. New ULP's, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. ULP Alonso Macias, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Farah [folder 1 of 2], 1970 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  3/70 -12/70
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Farah ([folder 2 of 2], 1970 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. United Farm Workers, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  November 18, 1973
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Venceremos Organization, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Warehousing & Trucking, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Complaints, 1970-1973 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Consumer Picketing, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Detroit Demonstrations, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Advance Materials, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Buddy's Mens Shop 5-CC-727, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Magdalena Hernandez 28-CA-2519, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Gilbert Minjarez 28-CA-2210, 1970-1974 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Oscar S. Arellano 28-CA-2210, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Luis G. Alvarez 28-CA-2036, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Manuel Pedrosa 28-CA-2036, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Emilio Casillas 28-CA-2036, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Manuel Montoya 28-CA-2036, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Daniel Olivas 28-CA-2054, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Juventino Morales 28-CA-2036, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Ramon Jurado, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Mario Porras 28-CA-2097, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Jose Villagran 28-CA-2036, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Carlos Vera 28-CA-2097, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Jose Velarde 28-CA, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Richard Valenzuela 28-CA, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Gerardo Ciriza 28-CA-2054, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Clemente Escalante 28-CA-2054, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Roberto S. Rodriquez 28-CA-2054, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Ramon F. Rios 28-CA-2054, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Hector E. Caballero 28-CA-2089, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Jesus J. Espinoza 28-CA-2089, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Manuel Porras 28-CA-2089, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Guadalupe Pineda 28-CA-2097, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Ernie Marrufo 28-CA-2097, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Ruben I. Lucero 28-CA, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Elvia V. Corral, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Guillermo Chavez 28-CA-2097, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Rosa Maria Castro 28-CA-2099, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Gregorio Gutierrez 28-CA-2099, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Ricardo Jose Carmona 28-CA-2099, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Manuel Bonilla 28-CA, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Johnny Rodriquez 28-CA-2126, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Lorenzo Rivas 28-CA-2126, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Ernesto Alfaro Jr. 28-CA-2126, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Farah Affidavits, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Farah ULP 28-CA-2036, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Union Labels, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. (Bat) Forms - Interrogatories, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Burt Beck Clearance Materials, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Farah 6/69 - 5/70 [folder 1 of 3], 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Farah 6/69 - 5/70 [folder 2 of 3], 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Farah 6/69 - 5/70 [folder 1 of 3], 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Farah - Cutting 28-RC-2054 Briefs [folder 1 of 2], 1972 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Farah - Cutting 28-RC-2054 Briefs [folder 2 of 2], 1970 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Annual Reports, 1968-1973 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Edmundo Ruiz ACWA Copy, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Consuela Soria ACWA Copy, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Blanca Dominguez ACWA Copy, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Armando Telles ACWA Copy, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Cipriana Telles ACWA Copy, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Malicious Prosecution Suits, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Farah - Cutting 28-RC-2054 [folder 1 of 2], 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  1/71 to 5/72
- Farah - Cutting 28-RC-2054 [folder 2 of 2], 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Cutting - 28-RC-2054 [folder 1 of 2], 1970 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  May-December
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Cutting - 28-RC-2054 [folder 2 of 2], 1970 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. CA Settlement [folder 1 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. CA Settlement [folder 2 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Farah - Shipping 185 NLRB No.92 (28-RC-2023) Briefs [folder 1 of 2], 1970 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Farah - Shipping 185 NLRB No.92 (28-RC-2023) Briefs [folder 2 of 2], 1970 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Farah Mfg. Co. Re-Employment Letters & Answers, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Farah - Shipping 185 NLRB No.92 (28-RC-2023), 1970 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Statements, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 11)